So, for the first time ever, my show, Smart, Funny, and Black, in honor of Juneteenth,
will be live streamed to the world.
That's right, y'all.
This weekend, I'm bringing two free shows of Smart, Funny, and Black to Nashville, Tennessee.
But if you aren't in Nashville, Tennessee, then don't you worry,
because you will get to also enjoy Smart, Funny, and Black on Saturday, June 17th at 7 p.m. and 9 p.m. Central Standard Time.
All you got to do is go to amandaseals.com and sign up for the live stream link.
Do you hear what I said?
You got to go to amandaseals.com and sign up for the live stream link.
And you and your peoples can be right in the comfort of your own home,
having a good time with all of us at Smart, Funny, and Black.
See you there.
Well, you'll see me there.
I won't see.
You'll see me.
So, it's because it's a one-way situation, but it's going to be a time.